So now that we have all the words, what we need to do
我们已经有了所有的单词
is we need to encode all of our views as integers.
我们需要将所有影评用整数表示
So we're going to pass in the reviews
我们将传入影评
where every word is an integer and that's going
每个单词都是用一个整数表示
to go into our embedding layer.
并进入嵌入层
So the first step, which I'm going to leave to you,
第一步由你来完成
is to create a dictionary that is mapping these vocabulary
创建一个字典 将这些词汇单词
words into integers.
映射为整数
And one thing to know is that later we're
要记住的是之后
going to be padding our input vectors with zeros.
我们将用 0 填满输入向量空缺的部分
So that means that when we convert our words to integers,
所有当我们将单词转换为整数时
they have to start at one, they can't start at zero
它们要从 1 开始 不能从 0 开始
or the network's going to get confused.
否则网络会感到困惑
So then once you have this mapping,
映射好后
then you should convert our reviews,
然后应该转换影评
from like that list of reviews, convert all the words
从影评列表将所有单词
into integers.
转换为整数
So now we have all our reviews, but instead of words we
现在我们有了所有的影评 但不是单词
have integers.
而是整数
And then next, we need to change our labels
接着 我们需要将标签
from positive and negative into ones and zeros.
从“positive”和“negative”更改为 1 和 0
So our labels, if you open it up,
打开标签后
each review is labeled with a string.
会看到每个影评都有一个标签
Either positive or negative.
positive 或 negative
But we need those to be ones and zeros,
但是我们需要将其转换为 1 和 0
so that we can actually use it in our network
这样才能用到网络中
and calculate the cost.
并计算损失
So you can do that here, also.
可以在这里实现
And so if you built labels correctly,
如果正确地设置标签
then what you should see if you run this cell,
运行该单元后应该看到
is that there's actually one review that has no length.
实际上有一个影评没有长度
I'm not really sure why, I didn't look into it very much,
我不知道为何会这样 我没有仔细研究
but it's the problem because it's
但是个问题
going to end up kind of breaking things later.
因为最终会破坏网络
So we need to get rid of it.
我们需要把这条影评删掉
Secondly, there's some really long reviews in here.
其次 这里有一些非常长的影评
So one of them is, the longest one is 2,514 words long.
最长的是 2,514 个单词
So that is pretty, that is really long
这太长了
and it's much too long to put into our RNN
根本无法放入我们的 RNN 中
because it is going to take a really long time to train
因为当前网络需要太长的时间
that many steps in our current network.
训练这么多的步长
So what we're going to do instead
我们将
is just truncate every review down
每个影评截断到
to 200 steps, or 200 words.
200 个步长或 200 个单词
So for reviews shorter than 200 words,
对于小于 200 个单词的影评
we can just pad to the left with zeros.
我们直接在左侧添加 0
So for instance if, you can kind of see down here,
例如对于下面这个示例
so if the review is like best movie ever,
如果影评是“best movie ever”
then in numbers that would the 117, 18, and 128.
那么用数字表示 就是 117 18 和 128
Then this row would look like zero zero
这行就变成 0 0
zero zero for 197 zeros, and then the last three numbers
0 0 197 个 0 最后三个数字
are the integers corresponding to the words.
是单词对应的整数
Like that.
就像这样
But the first thing I want you to do
但首先你要做的是
is remove the review that has zero length.
删掉长度为 0 的影评
So you can do that here.
可以在这里实现
And then next create this array features
然后创建这个数组特征
that contains the data we'll pass to the network.
其中包含我们将传入网络的数据
So there's going to be one row for each review,
每个影评各占一行
and then there's going to be 200 steps, or 200 words,
每行有 200 个步长
in each row.
或 200 个单词
And then, like I was saying before, if you
然后正如我之前提到的
have a review that's less than 200 words, pad it to the left
如果影评少于 200 个单词 那么在左侧
with zeros.
填充 0
And then if it's more than 200 words,
如果多于 200 个单词
just use the first 200 words as this feature vector.
则仅使用前 200 个单词作为特征向量
So if you built features correctly,
如果正确构建特征的话
it should look something like this.
结果应该看起来这样
So for the first review, we just get a bunch of zeros,
对于第一条影评 大多数都是 0
and then here is our review.
这里是我们的影评
Then this is what it looks like for a review that
这是超过 200 个
had more than 200 characters.
字符的影评
So it looks like this.
看起来是这样
Where like this 200 element vector
这个 200 个元素的向量
is completely filled out with no padding.
完全填满 没有 0